// This file can be replaced during build by using the `fileReplacements` array.
// `ng build` replaces `environment.ts` with `environment.prod.ts`.
// The list of file replacements can be found in `angular.json`.

export const environment = {
  production: false,
  options: [
    {
      "question": "Frage 1?",
      "answer": "Antwort 1."
    },
    {
      "question": "Frage 2?",
      "answer": "Antwort 2."
    },
    {
      "question": "Frage 3?",
      "answer": "Antwort 3."
    },
    {
      "question": "Frage 4?",
      "answer": "Antwort 4."
    },
    {
      "question": "Frage 5?",
      "answer": "Antwort 5."
    },
    {
      "question": "Frage 6?",
      "answer": "Antwort 6."
    },
    {
      "question": "Frage 7?",
      "answer": "Antwort 7."
    },
    {
      "question": "Frage 8?",
      "answer": "Antwort 8."
    },
    {
      "question": "Frage 9?",
      "answer": "Antwort 9."
    },
    {
      "question": "Frage 10?",
      "answer": "Antwort 10."
    },
    {
      "question": "Frage 11?",
      "answer": "Antwort 11."
    },
    {
      "question": "Frage 12?",
      "answer": "Antwort 12."
    },
    {
      "question": "Frage 13?",
      "answer": "Antwort 13."
    },
    {
      "question": "Frage 14?",
      "answer": "Antwort 14."
    }
  ]
};

/*
 * For easier debugging in development mode, you can import the following file
 * to ignore zone related error stack frames such as `zone.run`, `zoneDelegate.invokeTask`.
 *
 * This import should be commented out in production mode because it will have a negative impact
 * on performance if an error is thrown.
 */
// import 'zone.js/plugins/zone-error';  // Included with Angular CLI.
